welcome back to another audacity
欢迎回到另一个大胆的地方
tutorial in this video I just want to go
这个视频中的教程我只想
over a couple more effects that's gonna
更多的影响 这将是
help our audio to sound better and also
帮助我们的音频听起来更好 而且
to work with silence and noise so I
在寂静和嘈杂中工作 所以我
recorded here some audio and we see just
在这里录制了一些音频 我们看到
by looking at it it's about 32 seconds
看着它 大约是32秒
long and it has a bunch of empty space
很长 而且它有一堆空地
empty silence in the beginning if we
空虚的沉默开始了 如果我们
just hit play it's empty over here
只要点击播放 这里就是空的
I'm just like is this thing on
我就像是这玩意儿开着吗
I'm just kind of like testing and has
我只是有点像是在做测试
some silence in here okay we're starting
安静一下 好的 我们要开始了
okay we're starting now okay got it so
好的 我们现在开始 好的 知道了
what I can do actually if you ever have
实际上我能做的是 如果你有
an audio file like this and sometimes
像这样的音频文件 有时
it'll be like an hour long there's
会有一个小时的时间
actually a nice effect or a nice tool in
实际上是一个很好的效果或一个很好的工具
audacity to remove all this silence what
厚颜无耻地打破这一切沉默什么
we do we just double click anywhere to
我们只需双击任意位置即可
select everything or press ctrl-a or go
选择所有内容或按Ctrl-a或Go
to edit we're going to select all once
要编辑 我们将选择全部一次
everything is all selected go to effects
一切都被选中了转到特效
and then we go to truncate silence and
然后我们去截断沉默和
this brings up we have some different
这说明我们有一些不同之处
options but I just leave it leave it the
选项 但我只是让它离开它
same unless you need to adjust it to try
相同 除非您需要调整以尝试
and then we just go to okay and look it
然后我们就去OK看一看
actually cuts out all that silence so
实际上打破了所有的沉默 所以
instead of being 30 seconds long now
而不是现在的30秒长
it's only 11 seconds long so it
只有11秒长 所以它
automatically detected any where there
自动检测到的任何位置
was a big gap of silence and then cut it
是一个很大的沉默缺口 然后就结束了
out cut most of it out it left some gaps
剪掉了大部分 留下了一些缝隙
of silence in here otherwise our audio
在这里的沉默 否则我们的音频
would just like run right in together to
就像正好碰上了一起
each other
彼此
but now we can play and see what this
但现在我们可以玩一玩 看看这是什么
sounds like are we on is this thing
听起来像是我们在一起就是这件事
recording is this thing on
正在录制的是这个东西
okay we're starting okay we're starting
好的 我们开始了好的 我们开始了
now okay so I said the same thing over
现在 好的 我重复了同样的话
and over again but it's didn't sound
一遍又一遍 但听起来并不像
quite so strange when I had a bunch of
很奇怪 当我有一堆
gaps in between alright but now what we
两者之间的差距好吧 但现在我们
can do we can take this audio and so
我们可以这样做 我们可以把这段音频
this part this first part actually I
这一部分这第一部分实际上我
didn't even play for you yet so maybe I
甚至还没有为你演奏 所以也许我
want to apply like a nice effect to just
我想要像一个好的效果一样应用到只是
this a nice echo effect so we go to
这是一个很好的回声效果 所以我们转到
effect so we go down to echo and we can
所以我们下到Echo 我们可以
actually say we can say delay this 0.1
实际上说我们可以说延迟这个0.1
seconds we can preview
我们可以预览的秒数
so we can do that I'll just say okay so
所以我们可以这么做 我会说好的 所以
that gives us sort of like this an
这给了我们一种类似于
interesting effect we did this a little
有趣的效果我们做了一点
bit earlier to under effects we can also
早一点到下效果我们也可以
go to reverb
去混响
this will make it sound like I'm in like
这会让我听起来像是
a big a big room we'll just leave all
一个很大的房间 我们会把所有的东西
that the rest the same but just know you
其余的都一样 只是知道你
can play with this quite a bit and so
可以经常玩这个游戏 所以
[Music]
[音乐]
another thing I should show you here
另一件我应该在这里展示给你们看的东西
what was it oh yeah okay of course so
那是什么 哦 好的 当然 那么
this makes it sound like I'm in like a
这让我听起来像是在
big hall kind of if I want to change
如果我想换衣服的话
some of this here to sound like I can
这里的一些话听起来像是我可以
select all this part here and let's go
在这里选择所有这一部分 然后我们走
to effects we can go to equalization and
对于效果 我们可以达到均衡和
there's a bunch of different profiles
有一堆不同的个人资料
here so if you're not familiar with this
在这里 如果你不熟悉这个
it's kind of outside the scope of this
这有点超出了我们的范围
video and actually I don't do a whole
视频 实际上我并没有做一个完整的
lot with this but I know like there's
很多事情 但我知道好像有
different frequencies of the audio and
音频和音频的不同频率
we can change different portions of it
我们可以改变它的不同部分
so a lot of times you'll see like this
所以很多时候你会看到这样的场景
will be like a lot of our base over here
会像我们在这里的很多基地一样
and this will be like a lot of our
这将会像我们的许多
treble so we can change this to affect
三倍 这样我们就可以改变这一点以影响
the way that musics going to sound but
音乐听起来的方式 但是
there's also some pre-selected curves
还有一些预选的曲线
for like AM radio this kind of gives
对于像AM收音机这样的人来说
that effect of an AM radio which is like
调幅收音机的效果就像
not much bass at all not much trouble at
没有太多的低音 没有太多的麻烦
all and it sounds more like this
这一切听起来更像是这样
recording which you might not not notice
录制您可能没有注意到的内容
a big difference there this is like
这里有很大的不同 这就像
walkie talkie which is even more extreme
对讲机 更极端的是
so you know that effect of talking into
所以你知道谈话对你的影响
a walkie talkie just sounds like very
对讲机听起来很像
kind of like hollow and like shallow sea
有点像空洞 像浅海
and we can even get more we can if we
我们甚至可以得到更多 如果我们
affect this a little bit we can even get
稍微影响一下 我们甚至可以得到
more of that effect by just going like
更多的效果 只要像这样
that C sounds like GI Joe kind of
那个C听起来有点像大兵乔
talking into the radio anyway and so we
不管怎样对着收音机说话 所以我们
can we can go okay we can actually
我们可以去吗？好的 我们真的可以
change that wave to to be that effect so
把那个波浪变成这样的效果
just know under here Equalization you
只知道在这里均衡你
can change a lot you can have some
可以改变很多 你可以拥有一些
different presets bass boost will just
不同的预置低音提升器
sigh boost the bass of course we got
叹息 增强贝斯 我们当然得到了
treble boost boost is the treble and so
高音助推就是高音助推
some different things we can do here
我们可以在这里做一些不同的事情
and then also we've got effects
然后我们也得到了一些影响
normalize will kind of just normalize
正常化将只是正常化
our audio and there's some different
我们的音频有一些不同
sayings we can leave it we can preview
我们可以离开它 我们可以预览
and see what it sounds like so it
看看它听起来像什么 所以它
actually makes our audio sound a lot
实际上让我们的音频听起来很棒
better it takes our wave and just kind
更好的是它需要我们的挥手和善意
of averages and it's called
它被称为平均数
normalization but even though with that
正常化 但即使有了
walkie-talkie it makes our just our
对讲机 它使我们只是我们的
audio sound a lot better so those are a
音频效果要好得多 所以这些都是
few things you can do you normalize your
你可以做的几件事让你的生活正常化
audio play with the equalization of
音频播放与均衡
course supply like effects and different
课程设置的相似效果和不同
probably not so much echo but the reverb
可能没有太多回声 但有混响
can give it if you do it subtly the
如果你巧妙地做到这一点 你可以给它
reverb can just give a nice little
混响可以给人一种美妙的感觉
subtle effect if we take it down and you
如果我们把它取下来 而你
know have some of this stuff not be just
我知道有些东西不只是
kind of gives it more of a feel of like
给人一种更像是
a more of a presence yeah that's why I'm
更多的存在是的 这就是为什么我
going to share with you in this video
我将在这段视频中与你分享
just a quick one go and play with those
只是一个快速的去玩那些
get familiar with them and I'll catch
去熟悉他们 我会抓住他们的
you in the next video
下一个视频中的你